Guide to the Women's and Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements (LGBT) Periodicals Collection, 1957-2017 RL.01399
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Addition, 2009
  - Lesbian Contradiction, no. 44 (Box 57)
  - Lesbian Feminist Flyer, Vol. 4, no. 6 (Box 57)
  - Lesbian Inciter, Vol. 1, no. 15 (Box 57)
  - The Lesbian Review of Books, Vol. 1, no. 1-3; Vol. 2, no. 2-4; Vol. 3, no. 1-4; Vol. 4, no. 1; Vol. 5, no. 1, 3 (Box 57)
  - Lesbian Rights Project, Vol. 1, no. 1-2; Vol. 2, nn; 1987 Fall (Box 58)
  - Lesbian Tide, Vol. 3, no. 11; Vol. 4, no. 1; Vol. 5, no. 2; Vol. 9, no. 2 (Box 58)
  - Lesbian Visual Artists, 1991 Summer; 1992 Summer; 1993 Fall; 1994 Summer; 1996 Spr/Sum; nn (Statement of Purpose), nn (LVA and Visibility) (Box 58)
  - Lesbian Voices, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 58)
  - Lesbians on the Loose, Vol. 9, no. 2; Vol. 10, no. 10-11; Vol. 11, no. 1-7, 9-10; Vol. 12, no. 1-3, 6-12; Vol. 13, no. 1-2, 4-7, 9-11; Vol. 14, no. 1, 6, 8 (Box 58)
  - Lezzie Smut, no. 4 (Box 58)
  - Liberation, Vol. 15, no. 10 (Box 58)
  - Libido, Vol. 3, no. 4; Vol. 5, no. 1, 3 (Box 58)
  - Lilith, 1968 Fall; Vol. 1, no. 1-3 (Box 59)
  - Ludus, 1993 Feb/March (Box 59)
  - Maize: A Lesbian Country Magazine, no. 26-27, 34, 38, 41-42, 44-45, 47-53, 55, 61, 65, 70-73 (Box 59)
  - Majority Report, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 59)
  - The Male Figure, no. 33 (Box 59)
  - Mama Bears News and Notes, Vol. 2, no. 4, 6 (Box 59)
  - Mama Raga, 2004 Nov, Dec; 2005 Apr (Box 59)
  - Manorama, no. 25 (Box 59)
  - Manpower!, no. 2 (Box 59)
  - Manual, no. 58, 64-66, 68 (Box 60)
  - Masque: Revue des Homosexualites, no. 4 (Box 60)
  - Mom's Apple Pie: Lesbian Mothers' National Defense Fund Newsletter, 1974; 1975 June; 1978 Oct; 1979 Summer; 1980 March/Apr; 1987 Summer (Box 60)
  - Moxie, Vol. 2, no. 2-3 (Box 60)
  - Ms., Vol. 1, no. 8, 10-12; Vol. 2, no. 1; Vol. 3, no. 3-6, 10, 12; Vol. 4, no. 1-8 (Box 60)
  - Ms., Vol. 4, no. 9-11; Vol. 5, no. 2, 7-9; Vol. 6, no. 1 (1977 July), 4-9, 12; Vol. 7, no. 5-10, 12; Vol. 8, no. 1, 4, 7-10; Vol. 9, no. 5; Vol. 13, no. 9 (Box 61)
  - Ms., Vol. 16, no. 8-9; (1990) Vol. 1, no. 1; (1990) Vol. 2, no.3 (Box 62)
  - Muscleboy, Vol. 2, no. 4-6 (Box 62)
  - My Trip Around the World (Box 62)
  - NACLA's Latin America and Empire Report, Vol. 6, no. 10 (Box 62)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League Campus Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 62)
  - National Center for Lesbian Rights Newsletter, 1991 Spr/Sum; 1992 Spring; 1993 Fall; 1994 Spring, Fall; 1998 Spring; 1999 Fall; 2004 Spring (Box 62)
  - National Times, Vol. 26, no. 5; Vol. 33, no. 2 (Box 62)
  - New York Feminist Tribune, 1970 May 2 (Box 62)
  - New York Pride Guide, 1989; 1991-1993 (Box 62)
  - A Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 62)
  - The Newsletter, Vol. 4, no. 13; Vol. 5, no. 1-3, 13; Vol. 8, no. 5, 7; Vol. 11, no. 15, 17-20, 22 (1992 Feb), 3 (1992 March), 34 (1992 April), 5-12 (1992 May-Dec); Vol. 12, no. 1, 3-7, 9-12; Vol. 13, no. 1-6, 8-12; Vol. 14, no. 3-7; Vol. 15, no. 1-8 (Box 62)
  - Nosotras, no. 1 (Box 62)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur, 1982 March (Box 62)
  - Of a Like Mind, Vol. 4, no. 1 (Box 63)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 1, no. 19; Vol. 17, no. 7-9; Vol. 21, no. 1; Vol. 22, no. 5; Vol. 23, no. 3-4 (Box 63)
  - Older Women's League (San Francisco Chapter Newsletter), 1997 Sept (Box 63)
  - The OLOC Reporter, Vol. 5, no. 3; Vol. 7, no. 2; Vol. 8, no. 1; Vol. 9, no. 4; Vol. 11, no. 4; Vol. 12, no. 3 (Box 63)
  - On Our Backs, Vol. 1, no. 2-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-2, 4-5; Vol. 3, no. 2-5; Vol. 4, no. 3; Vol. 5, no. 2-6; Vol. 6, no. 1-6, Vol. 7, no.1; Vol. 9, no. 5-6; Vol. 15, no. 2 (Box 63)
  - On Our Backs, Vol. 7, no. 3-6; Vol. 8, no. 1-6; Vol. 9, no. 1-4; Vol. 10, no. 1-4; Vol. 10 (1995), no. 2; Vol. 11, no. 1; Vol. 13, no. 1-2, Vol. 14, no. 3 (Jun/Jul), 3 (Oct/Nov), 4-6; Vol. 15, no. 3; Vol. 16, no. 4; Vol. 17 (2003), no. 4 (Dec/Jan); Vol. 18, no. 1; Vol. 19, no. 2 (Box 64)
  - On the Issues, Vol. 6-8, 18 (Box 64)
  - One, Vol. 3, no. 1, 3-4; Vol. 5, no. 1, 6; Vol. 6, no. 1, 5, 8; Vol. 7, no. 2, 4-8; Vol. 8, no. 5-6, 9, 11-12; Vol. 9, no. 2 (Box 64)
  - One, Vol. 6, no. 7, 10, 12; Vol. 7, no. 1, 3, 9, 11; Vol. 8, no. 1-2, 11-12; Vol. 9, no. 1; Vol. 14, no. 2 (Box 65)
  - Onyx: Black Lesbian Newsletter, Vol. 3, no. 1 (Box 65)
  - Le Operaie della Casa, 1975 Maggio 1 (Box 65)
  - Out and About, 1978 Sept-Nov; 1979 June, Sept; 1980 Sept, Nov-Dec; 1981 Jan-Feb (Box 65)
  - Outlook, no. 6, 11 (Box 65)
  - Peacetalks, no. 17 (Box 65)
  - Pentimenta, 1996/1997 Winter; 1997 nn; 1998 Summer (Box 65)
  - Physique Illustrated, no. 4 (Box 65)
  - Plainswoman, Vol. 8, no. 4-5; Essays (Box 65)
  - Poder y Libertad, no. 18 (Box 65)
  - Poets and Writers, Vol. 20, no. 1 (Box 65)
  - Power of Women, Vol. 1, no. 3-5 (Box 65)
  - Prime Time, Vol. 1, no. 11 (Box 65)
  - Pucker Up, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 65)
  - Push, Vol. 1, no. 2, 4 (Box 65)
  - Quest, Vol. 3, no. 4 (Box 65)
  - RFD (Radical Fairies Digest), no. 34, 37, 49, 55, 65, 71 (Box 65)
  - Ramparts, Vol. 6, no. 7 (Box 66)
  - RAT Subterranean News, no. 20 (Box 66)
  - Redstockings: Feminist Revolution (Box 66)
  - Roger, no. 1, 2 (Box 66)
  - Sappho, Vol. 3, no. 10 (Box 66)
  - Sassy, Vol. 4, no. 4, 6-7, 10; Vol. 5, no. 2-3, 6-7; Vol. 6, no. 2, 6-7; Vol. 8, no. 7-10; Vol. 9, no. 3 (Box 66)
  - Sessualita procreazione maternita aborto (Box 67)
  - She, Vol. 1, no. 3-4, 6-7; Vol. 6. no. 4-7, 11-12 (Box 67)
  - Sinister Wisdom, no. 20 (Box 67)
  - Sir Gee, no. 14 (Box 67)
  - Sister, Vol. 4, no. 12; Vol. 7, no. 1 (Box 67)
  - Society for Humane Abortion, Inc. Newsletter, Vol. 3, no. 2; Vol. 4, no. 1; Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 67)
  - Sojourner, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 67)
  - So's Your Old Lady, 1976 March, May; no. 11, 22 (Box 67)
  - Sottosopra, 1976 March (Box 67)
  - Spare Rib, no. 63 (Box 67)
  - Spartan for Men, no. 3 (Box 67)
  - Spectre, no. 6 (Box 67)
  - Storyletters, no. 2 (Box 67)
  - Super Studs, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 67)
  - Third Wave: The Next Step in Philanthropy and Feminism, 1998 Spr/Sum (Box 67)
  - Tooth and Nail, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 67)
  - Tres Femmes, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 67)
  - Trigger, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 67)
  - Trim Studio Quarterly, no. 9 (Box 67)
  - Unique, no. 3 (Box 67)
  - Up from Under, Vol. 1, no. 1-3 (Box 67)
  - Uranus, no. 1 (Box 68)
  - Vector, Vol. 6, no. 8; Vol. 8. no. 8 (Box 68)
  - La Vie en Rose, no. 16-17 (Box 68)
  - Vim, no. 13 (Box 68)
  - Vindacacion Feminista, no. 1-2 (Box 68)
  - Visibilities, Vol. 2, no. 5 (Box 68)
  - Visions, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 68)
  - Voice of the Women's Liberation Movement, 1968 Aug (Box 68)
  - A Web of Crones, 1985 Spring-Winter (Box 68)
  - Win, Vol. 12, no. 8 (Box 68)
  - The Wise Woman, Vol. 6, no. 4; Vol. 7, no.3-4; Vol. 8, no. 1, 3-4; Vol. 9, no. 1-4; Vol. 10, no. 1-4; Vol. 11, no. 1-4; Vol. 13, no. 1 (Box 68)
  - The Wishing Well, Vol. 5, no. 4; Vol. 7, no. 1; Vol. 8, no. 3 (Box 68)
  - The Woman Activist, 1972 Dec (Box 68)
  - Woman of Power, no. 17 (Box 68)
  - Woman Spirit, Vol. 1, no. 3; Vol. 2, no. 7, Vol. 6, no. 24 (Box 69)
  - Womanews, Vol. 1, no. 2, 5, 7; Vol. 2, no. 1-8, 10; Vol. 3, no. 2, 4, 6-8, 10; Vol. 4, no. 1-2, 4, 7; Vol. 5, no. 3-4; Vol. 8, no. 10; Vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 69)
  - Woman's World, Vol. 1, no. 1-2 (Box 69)
  - Women: A Journal of Liberation, Vol. 1, no. 3-4; vol. 4, no. 1, 3; Vol. 5, no. 1-3 (Box 69)
  - Women Energy, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 70)
  - Women of Color News, Vol. 2, no. 2-4 (Box 70)
  - The Women's Page, 1970 Aug (Box 70)
  - Women's Review, Vol. 10, no. 1 (Box 70)
  - The Women's Review of Books, Vol. 1, no. 1-11; Vol. 2, no. 2-10, 12; Vol. 3, no. 1-2 (Box 70)
  - The Women's Review of Books, Vol. 3, no. 3-4, 6-10, 12; Vol. 4, no. 1-5, 7, 9-12; Vol. 5, no. 2, 6; Vol. 9, no. 5 (Box 71)
  - Women's Struggle Notes, no. 1 (Box 71)
  - The Wree-View, 1981 Aug/Sept (Box 71)
  - Young Guys!, no. 2 (Box 71)
  - The Young Physique, Vol. 6, no. 6 (Box 71)
- Addition, 2011
  - American Man, Vol. 2 no. 4 (Box 72)
  - Bad Attitude, Vol. 1, no.1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-3; Vol. 3, no. 1-3; Vol. 4, no. 1,3 (Box 72)
  - Calyx, Vol. 10, no. 1 (Box 72)
  - Cherry Blossoms, no. 4 (Box 72)
  - Conditions, no. 2, 14 (Box 72)
  - Crystal Crone, no. 1 (Box 72)
  - Dungeon Master, No. 1-12, 14, 18-20, 24-38; Yearbook 1 (Box 72)
  - Fireweed, Summer/Fall 1985 (Box 72)
  - IKON, Second Series, no. 1-10 (Box 73)
  - Knotty, Vol. 2 no. 11 (Box 73)
  - Mach Quarterly, no. 1-4, 8-9, 13-16 (Box 73)
  - Manifest Reader, no. 1-2 (Box 73)
  - No Apologies, no. 2 (Box 73)
  - Obeisance, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 73)
  - Outrageous Women, Vol. 1, no. 1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-4; Vol. 3, no. 1-3 (Box 74)
  - Pandora, no. 5, 7 (Box 74)
  - Paragraph, no. 1-2 (Box 74)
  - The Power Exchange, Vol. 1, no. 3-4 (Box 74)
  - The Sandmutopia Garden and Dungeon Journal, no. 1, 2, 4, 5 (Box 74)
  - Skin Two, no. 3, 6-10 (Box 74)
  - Taste of Latex, no. 6 (Box 74)
  - Tribe, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 74)
  - I Know You Know, Vol. 1, no. 1-6 (Box 74)
  - Visibilities, Vol. 1, no. 1; Vol. 2 no. 2-5 (Box 74)
  - Onna Erosu, no. 1 (Box 74)
  - Center Happenings, July 1986; Sept. 1988; Dec. 1997/Jan.1998; Feb./Mar. 1998/ Mar./April 1998 (Box 74)
  - Sage Newsletter, Jan. 1979, Spring 1983, Winter 1988, June 1989, Spring 1990, Winter 2003, Spring 2004, Summer 2007, Winter 2008 (Box 74)
  - The Center Voice, Vol. 4 no. 4; Vol. 6, no.6; Vol. 16, no. 6; Vol. 14, no. 1 (Box 74)
  - Task Force Report (Newsletter of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1984 (?), Sept. 1985, Nov. 1985, Summer 1986, Winter 1988-Winter/Spring 1990 (Box 75)
  - HX for Her, no. 42, 59, 60 (Box 75)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives Newsletter, no. 17 (Box 75)
  - Young Voices, June/July 1985, Fall 1987, Winter 1988, February 1989 (Box 75)
  - Hot Wire, Vol. 4, no. 1-3; Vol. 5, no. 1; Vol. 6, no. 3 (Box 75)
  - On Our Backs, Vol. 4, no. 1,2,4; Vol. 5, no. 1; Vol. 7, no. 4-5 (Box 75)
  - MetroSource, Winter 1997-Spring 1998 (Box 75)
  - NYQ, no. 4, 6, 17, 20-21, 23, 26 (Box 75)
  - QW, no. 33, 41,42, 51, 53, 55 (Box 75)
  - Outweek, no. 62, 71, 82, 89 (Box 75)
  - Astrea Bulletin, Spring 1985, Winter 1998, Summer 1998, Fall 2003 (Box 76)
  - HX, no. 338 (Box 76)
  - Tradeswomen, Summer 1983 (Box 76)
  - FAAR and NCN, July/August, 1978 (Box 76)
  - Aegis, Sept./Oct. 1978-1986 (Box 76)
  - Women in Struggle, June-August 1973 (Box 76)
  - Dragon, no. 9 (Box 76)
  - The New Woman's Clinic, Inc. Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 76)
  - Women Together, Vol. 1, no. 7, 9 (Box 76)
  - Winnipeg Women's Liberation Newsletter, Oct. 1974, Jan.-Mar. 1975, Oct. 1975, June 1976 (Box 76)
  - Eastern Region Producers Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 1-2; Vol. 2, no. 1-5 (Box 76)
  - Tooth and Nail, Vol., no. 1 (Box 76)
  - The Women Artists Group News, Vol. 2, no. 9; Vol. 3, no. 1-4; Vol. 4, no. 1-4, 6-7; Vol. 5, no. 1-3, 6; Vol. 6, no. 1-11; Vol. 8, no. 3 (Box 76)
  - Bay Area Women's Liberation Newsletter, no. 1 (Box 77)
  - Act Now Newsletter, Feb.-Mar., May-June, Nov.-Dec. 1974 (Box 77)
  - Thesmophoria, Vol. 4, no. 4 (Box 77)
  - Workers World, Vol. 37, no. 15 (Box 77)
  - Workers Struggle Supplement, no. 3 (Box 77)
  - Pursuit and Symposium/BAG ONE, NO. 1-2 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Coast Times, Vol. 3, no. 6 (Box 77)
  - Win Magazine, Vol. 5, no. 20 (Box 77)
  - Pornography Awareness Newsletter, Spring 1986-Winter 1987, Spring 1989 (Box 77)
  - North Carolina WomeNews, Vol. 1, no. 1, 6, 8 (Box 77)
  - NC Equity Reports, Nov. 1987, Feb. 1988, June 1988, Sept. 1988, May 1989, Nov. 1991 (Box 77)
  - Madness Network News, Vol. 3, no. 6 (Box 77)
  - Listen Real Loud, Vol. 8, no. 2; Vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 77)
  - Black Women's Health Project News, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 77)
  - Quarterly Journal of the National Association for Mental Health, Vol. 57, no. 1 (Box 77)
  - Quality of Life Digest, March-April, 1983 (Box 77)
  - The Radical Therapist, Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 77)
  - Fag Rag Gay Sunshine, Summer 1974 (Box 77)
  - The Female Experience, 1973 (Box 77)
  - Durham YWCA Periodicals (incl. Women on the Move, Coalition Quarterly, News and Programs for Every Woman, Durham YWCA), 1983-1987 (Box 77)
  - Society for Humane Abortion, Inc. Newsletter, Vol. 6, no. 1-2, 4; Vol. 7, no. 1-2 (Box 77)
  - WONAAG Newsletter, 5/1/1972, 6/1/1972, 7/9/1972 (Box 77)
  - The Lesbian News, no. 24-28, 30, 32-33, 35, 37-38 (Box 77)
  - Issues! Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 77)
  - Lesbian Connection, Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 77)
  - Older Women's League Newsletter, Sept. 1988 (Box 77)
  - Womanbooks Review, Vol. 3, no. 5 (Box 77)
  - GLAAD Bulletin, May/June 1988 (Box 77)
  - Courage, no. 9 (Box 77)
  - In the Life, Vol. 6, no. 9 (Box 77)
  - Lilith, no. 8, 10 (Box 77)
  - Lesbenpresse, no. 11 (Box 77)
  - Rundbrief Lesbenarchiv, no. 3 (Box 77)
  - Frankenfurter Frauenblatt, Sept. 1983 (Box 77)
  - Emma, Vol. 5, no. 9 (Box 77)
  - Lesbenfront, no. 15 (Box 78)
  - Sappho's Isle, Vol. 2, no. 4, 9 (Box 78)
  - The Lesbian Review of Books, Vol. 4, no. 4 (Box 78)
  - GLAAD Newsletter, Winter/Spring 1987 (Box 78)
  - Matrix Newsletter, Fall 1988 (Box 78)
  - Majority Report, Vol. 4, no. 12 (Box 78)
  - Belles Lettres, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 78)
  - Hurricane Alice, Vol. 3, no. 4; Vol. 4, no. 4 (Box 78)
  - Our Paper, Vol. 6, no. 10 (Box 78)
  - The Fund for Human Dignity, Spring 1989 (Box 78)
  - The Political Economy of Women, Vol. 4, no. 3 (Box 78)
  - Clothed with the Sun, Vol. 6, no. 2 (Box 78)
  - National Anti-Pornography Civil Rights Organization Reporter, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 78)
  - Symposium Newsletter, Jan. 11-12, 1985 (Box 78)
  - Maryland Commission for Women Newsletter, Fall 1984 (Box 78)
  - WHISPER, Vol. 1, no. 1-3; Vol. 2, no. 1-3; Vol. 3, no. 2-3; Vol. 4, no. 2; Vol. 5, no. 1-3; Vol. 6, no. 1-2; Vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 78)
  - Women Against Pornography Newsreport, Fall 1982, Vol. 5, no. 1-2; Vol. 8, no. 1-2 (Box 78)
  - Wordwrite: Femrite Literary Journal, Vol. 1, 3, 5 (Box 78)
  - New Era, no. 4-8, 10-16 (Box 78)
  - Femrite, 2000 (Box 78)
  - Issues Quarterly, Vol. 1, no. 1, 4; Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 78)
  - Sfinga, no. 1-2 (Box 78)
  - Pro Femina, no. 1-6, 27-28 (Box 79)
  - Synthesis, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 79)
  - Agenda, no. 35, 37, 38, 39, 41, Monograph 1999, 42, 44, 47 (Box 79)
  - Agenda, 49, 51-53 (Box 80)
  - 75 Percent, no. 1-2 (Box 80)
  - AWID Spotlight, no. 4 (Box 80)
  - Women, Vol. 1, no. 1,3,4; Vol. 2, no. 2-3 (Box 80)
  - The Human Factor, Vol. 10, no. 1 (Box 80)
  - Up from Under, Vol. 1. no. 1-4 (Box 80)
  - Triple Jeopardy, Vol. 4, no. 1 (Box 80)
  - Female Liberation Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 80)
  - Radical Historians, no. 48 (Box 80)
  - Women's Liberation Newsletter, Vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 80)
  - Peking Review, no. 39 (Box 80)
  - WIN, Vol. 15, no. 5-6, 29, 33 (Box 80)
  - Yake Break, Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 80)
  - Red Rag, no. 3, 11, 12 (Box 80)
  - Women's World, no. 32 (Box 80)
  - Political Environments, no. 2-5 (Box 80)
  - Transitions, Vol. 5, no. 1 (Box 81)
  - Network of East-West Women, Winter and Fall 1984 (Box 81)
  - Network of East-West Women Online Bulletin, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 81)
  - Lola Press, no. 1, 8, 10 1/2 (Box 81)
  - Fair Play, no. 2-4, 6-8 (Box 81)
  - Power of Words (Russian Title), no. 2 (Box 81)
  - The Women's Dialogue, no. 6 (22), 13 (29), 15/31, 17/33, 25/41 (Box 81)
  - Kanga, Vol. 1, no. 2-5, 2 special issues (Box 81)
  - Grumin, 2nd year, International no. 2 (Box 81)
  - Mujer/Fempress, Special Issue, no. 111, 123 (Box 81)
  - Do It Now, Vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 81)
  - National NOW Times, Vol. 11, no. 8, 9, 12; Vol. 13, no. 6; Vol. 14, no. 6; Vol. 15, no. 2, 3, 9/10; Vol. 16, no. 1-2; Vol. 17, no. 2, 3, 5; Vol. 18, no. 7; Vol. 19, no. 2; Vol. 20, no. 2, 3; Vol. 22, no. 1, 2 (Box 81)
  - 10 Percent, Vol. 1, no. 3-5; Vol. 2, no. 6 (Box 82)
  - Curve, Vol. 6, no. 1-3, 5-6; Vol. 7, no. 1-6; Vol. 8, no. 1-6; Vol. 9, no. 1-6; Vol. 10, no. 2-7 (Box 82)
  - Deneuve, Vol. 1, no. 1, 3, 4; Vol. 2, no. 3,6; Vol. 3, no. 1, 2, 4, 5 (Box 82)
  - Deneuve, Vol. 4, no. 1-6; Vol. 5, no. 1, 2, 6 (Box 83)
  - On the Issues, Vol. 25, Winter 1992 (Box 83)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 5, no. 7-8; Vol. 6, no. 3-9; Vol. 17, no. 6 (Box 83)
  - Quicksilver Times Supplement, Oct. 1969 (Box 83)
  - Radical America, Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 83)
  - Gay Forum, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Oversize-box 1)
  - Gay Sunshine, no. 8, 12-13, 16, 33/34 (Oversize-box 1)
  - Gotham, Vol. 2, no. 13 (Oversize-box 1)
  - The Lesbian News, Vol. 18, no. 7, 12; Vol. 21, no. 1, 3-6 (Box OS2)
  - New York Blade, Vol. 2, no. 6, 8, 17 (Box OS2)
- Addition, 2012
  - The Advocate, no. 683 (Box 84)
  - Circles, March/April 1998 (Box 84)
  - Common Lives/Lesbian Lives, no. 6 (Box 84)
  - Deneuve, Vol. 2, no. 6; Vol 4, no. 1 (Box 84)
  - Feminary, Vol 9, no. 2 (Box 84)
  - Frontiers, Vol. 8, no. 2 (Box 84)
  - Gay Community News, Vol. 8, no. 45 (Box 84)
  - Heresies, Vol. 1, no. 4; Vol 2, no. 2-3; Vol. 4, no. 1, 3; Vol. 5, no. 1-2 (Box 84)
  - Heresies, Vol, 4; Vol. 5, no.102 (Box 85)
  - Jane and Jane, Vol. 3, no. 5 (Box 85)
  - Jump Cut, No. 24/25 (Box 85)
  - Lesbian Tide, Vol. 8, no. 6 (Box 85)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives News, no. 5 (Box 85)
  - Motive, Vol. 32, no. 1 (Box 85)
  - Musica, no. 56 (Box 85)
  - Music Women, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 85)
  - Ms., Vol. 9, no. 3 (Box 85)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 10, no. 9; Vol 11, no. 5 (Box 85)
  - Off Our Backs, Vol. 1, No. 3; July 10, 1970 (Box 85)
  - On Our Backs, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 85)
  - Rockrgrl, no. 1, 53 (Box 85)
  - SageWoman, no. 28 (Box 85)
  - Sojourner, Vol. 5, no. 11; Vol. 6, no. 11 (Box 85)
  - Troubadoura, no. 5 (Box 86)
  - Aphra, Vol. 1, no. 1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-3; Vol. 4, no. 3 (Box 86)
  - Chrysalis, no. 4 (Box 86)
  - The Furies, Feb. 1972 (incomplete); Vol. 1. no. 5, 7; Vol. 2, no. 2-3 (Box 86)
  - Leviathan, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 86)
  - Liberation, Vol 16, no. 9 (Box 86)
  - Majority Report, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 86)
  - Manhattan Tribune, Vol. 2, no. 23 (Box 86)
  - The Mole, Vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 86)
  - Mushroom Effect, 1970 (Box 86)
  - The Radical Therapist, Vol. 1, no. 3 (Box 86)
  - Red Rag, no. 12 (Box 86)
  - The Second Wave, Vol. 1, no. 4 (Box 86)
  - Quicksilver Times Supplement, Oct. 1969 (Box 86)
  - Women, Vol. 1, no. 1-4 (Box 86)
  - Women, Vol. 2, no. 2-4; Vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 87)
  - Source, Vol. 3, no. 1 (Box 87)
  - Up from Under, Vol. 1, no. 1-2, 4 (Box 87)
  - Crossroads, no. 29 (Box 87)
  - Echoes from the Sanctuary, Aug. 1992 (Box 87)
  - Letters from Harriet, no. 9 (Box 87)
  - The Nuditarian, Vol. 2, no. 8 (Box 87)
  - Booklegger Magazine, Vol. 1, no. 1-6; Vol. 2, no. 7-10, 12; Vol. 3, no. 13-15 (Box 87)
  - Emergency Librarian, Vol. 1, no. 4-6; Vol. 2, no. 1-6 (Box 87)
  - Emergency Librarian, Vol. 3, no. 1-2, 4-6; Vol. 4, no. 1-3, 5-6; Vol. 5, no. 1-5 (Box 88)
  - Synergy, no. 34-42 (Box 88)
  - Identity House Journal, Winter 1991 (Box 88)
  - Advocate, no. 333, 428 (Box 88)
  - Curve, Vol. 11, no. 1-2 (Box 88)
  - Out, no. 43-44, 46-52 (Box 89)
- Addition, 2013
  - Sing Out!, Vol. 25, no. 2 (Box 89)
  - Folk Roots, No. 48 (Box 89)
  - Spare Rib, No. 122, 127 (Box 89)
  - Shewolf's Directory of Wimmin's Lands, 4th ed. (2003-2005) (Box 89)
  - Voices, Spring 1993, Winter 1994 (Box 89)
  - Community Connections, Vol. 6, no. 5, 7-11; Vol. 7, no. 1-5 (Box 89)
  - The Monthly Extract, Vol. 5, no. 1-3; Vol. 6, no. 1-2 (Box 89)
  - Paid My Dues, no. 6; Vol. 2, no. 3; Vol. 3, no. 1-2, 4 (Box 89)
- Addition, 2014
  - The Barb, v. 3, no. 7; v. 4, no. 5 (Box 90)
  - Mississippi Voice, v. 1, no. 3; v. 3, no. 8; v. 4, no. 2-12; v. 5, no. 1-4, 9 (Box 90)
  - This Month in Mississippi, v. 18, no. 2 (Box 90)
  - Alabama Forum, v. 17, no. 11; v. 18, no. 1-2, 6-7, 10-12; v. 19, no. 1, 5-10, 12; v. 20, no. 1-3, 6-12; v. 21, no. 1-2 (Box 90)
  - At the Crossroads, no. 1-7 (Box 91)
  - Woman of Power, no. 18-22, 24 (Box 91)
  - Heresies, v. 2, no. 1; v. 6, no. 1 (Box 91)
  - Sinister Wisdom, v. 50, 52 (Box 91)
  - On the Issues, v. 2, no. 4; v. 3, no. 1, 2, 4; v. 5, no. 3; v. 6, no. 4; v. 7, no. 1-3, v. 8, no. 1 (Box 92)
  - Lesbian Ethics, v. 5, no. 1-3 (Box 92)
  - Quest, v. 5, no. 1-2 (Box 92)
  - No More Fun and Games, v. 2-3, 5 (Box 92)
  - Gossip, v. 6 (Box 92)
  - Feminary, v. 11, no. 1-2 (Box 92)
  - Fireweed, no. 13-15, 25-26, 36 (Box 93)
  - Trivia, v. 14-15, 18-19, 21 (Box 93)
  - Antiracism Newsletter, v. 1 (Box 93)
  - Practicing Antiracism, v. 2-6 (Box 93)
  - Hothead Paisan, v. 1-11 (Box 93)
  - Common Lives Lesbian LIves, v. 7, 13, 26 (Box 93)
  - Lady-Unique-Inclination-Of-The-Night, v. 6 (Box 93)
  - The Widening Circle, v. 1 (Box 93)
  - Under the Sign of Pices, v. 5, no. 4 (Box 93)
  - Womanart, v. 1, no. 1-2, 4; v. 2, no. 3 (Box 94)
  - Forte, v. 1, no. 1-2; v. 2, no. 1, 3 (Box 94)
  - Plexus, v. 10, no. 11; v. 11, no. 3 (Box 94)
  - Women's Caucus for Art Newsletter, v. 10, no. 1-2 (Box 94)
  - The Celibate Woman, v. 1, no. 2 (Box 94)
  - Media Report to Women, v. 9, no 14; v. 13, no. 5 (Box 94)
  - Hue Points, v. 13, no. 1 (Box 94)
  - Heresies, v. 4, no. 2, 4 (Box 94)
  - Arena Review, v. 8, no. 2 (Box 94)
  - Alternative Media, v. 12, no. 3 (Box 94)
  - Women's Resource and Action Center Newsletter, September 1983 (Box 94)
  - Spokeswoman, v. 11, no. 6 (Box 94)
  - On the Issues, v. 6 (Box 94)
  - Dade Times, v. 6 (Box 94)
  - ATF News, v. 5, no. 3 (Box 94)
  - Womanist: A Newsletter for Afrocentric Feminist Researchers, v. 1, no. 2 (Box 94)
  - Womanist: Theory and Research, v. 2, no. 1 (Box 94)
  - Fuse, v. 16, no. 5 (Box 94)
  - Lambda Rising News, Summer 1992 (Box 94)
  - Green Line: New News for Western North Carolina, v. 5, no. 10 (Box 94)
  - Cassandra: Radical Feminist Nurses Newsjournal, v. 2, no. 2 (Box 94)
  - Connexions: International Women's Quarterly, v. 42 (Box 95)
  - Elizabeth Stone House Community Update, Spring 1984 (Box 95)
  - Labyrinth: The Philadelphia Women's Newspaper, v. 1 (Box 95)
  - Women's Times: A Newsletter of the Virginia Women's Studies Newsletter, Spring 1984 (Box 95)
  - A Shift in the Wind, v. 21 (Box 95)
  - The Tribune: A Women and Development Quarterly, v. 23, 27-31 (Box 95)
  - New Directions for Women, v. 12, no. 6; v. 13, no. 1-6; v. 14, no. 2-6; v. 15, no. 1-4 (Box 95)
  - New Directions for News, September 1983 (Box 95)
  - National NOW Times, v. 12, no. 4; v. 13, no. 5, 7-10, 12; v. 14, no. 2-10; v. 15, no. 1, 3-9; v. 16, no. 1, 3-9; v. 17, no. 1-6; v. 18, no. 1-2, 4-8; v. 19, no. 2-3 (Box 96)
  - Southern Feminist, v. 1, no. 1-3; v. 2, no. 1-3, 5-6; v. 3, no. 1-3 (Box 97)
  - Camping Women Trails (Box 97)
  - Women's Resource and Action Center News, April, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Woman Image Now, v. 2 (Box 97)
  - Lesbian Contradiction, v. 5 (Box 97)
  - Reveille, v. 126, no. 29 (Box 97)
  - Country Women, v. 1, no. 2 (Box 97)
  - Chrysalis, no. 5-6, 8 (Box 97)
  - Spectrum: A Cooperative Newspaper for the Tallahassee Community, no. 28 (Box 97)
  - Sojourner, v. 5, no. 8 (Box 97)
  - Off Our Backs, v. 10, no. 11; v.11, no. 9 (Box 97)
  - Dimensions, v. 5, no. 3, 6 (Box 97)
  - Carolina Lesbian News, v. 1-2 (Box 97)
  - Out in Black, v. 3.3 (Box 97)
  - CLOUTreach, v. 12, no. 1; v. 13, no. 1-3 (Box 97)
  - The Down East Voice, v. 3, no. 4 (Box 97)
  - Equality News, no. 16 (Box 98)
  - Gay People's Chronicle, v. 10, no. 21; v. 12, no. 18; v. 13, no. 5-11 (Box 98)
  - Woman's Monthly, v. 2, no. 6-7; v. 3, no. 1-2, 8 (Box 98)
  - Transgender Tapestry, no. 106 (Box 98)
- Addition, 2015-2016
  - The Ladder, v. 1, no. 8-9 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 2, no. 8-12 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 3, no. 1-3, 6, 8 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 4, no. 3-6, 11-12 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 5, no. 1-2, 12; v. 6, no. 1, 4-8 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 7, no. 1, 8-10 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 8, no. 2-6, 8, 11-12 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 9, no. 1-3, 5-8 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 10, no. 2-3, 6, 8-12 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 11, no. 2-11 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 12, no. 1-3, 8-10 (Box 99)
  - The Ladder, v. 13, no. 1-2 (Box 99)
  - Hot Wire, v. 8, no. 1-3; v. 9, no. 1-3; v. 10, no. 1-3 (Box 100)